keepbelieving.com 2008-05-20

# Privacy Policy

Keep Believing Ministries is committed to respecting your online privacy and security. We have developed this privacy policy to ensure our web visitors that information you provide to websites of Keep Believing Ministries will not be shared with any third party. 

**Awareness.** Keep Believing Ministries provides this Online Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy policy and security practices, and to inform you of the way your information is collected and used. We also provide you with the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so.

**Information Collected.** On some Keep Believing Ministries websites you can provide contact information for ministry-related purposes, to order resources, or to make ministry contributions. Here are the types of personal information that we collect:

  * contact information:  name, complete address, phone number, email address;
  * shipping information: name, complete address;
  * information concerning how you heard about Keep Believing Ministries;
  * information you wish to leave: questions, comments, suggestions; and 
  * your request to receive periodic updates: e.g., to individuals who request it, we will send weekly sermons and periodic e-mails related to specific fund-raising appeals and prayer concerns.

**How Information is Used.** Keep Believing Ministries uses your information to understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, communicate back to you, update you on ministry happenings, and to personalize our website for you. We use the comments you offer to provide you with information requested, and we take seriously each recommendation as to how we might improve communication. 

**No Sharing of Personal Information.** Keep Believing Ministries will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to other organizations. We assure you that the identity of all who contact us through our websites will be kept confidential. Use of personal information will be limited to the internal purposes of Keep Believing Ministries and only to further the ministry activities and purposes of Keep Believing Ministries.

**Cookies.** From time to time, we may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the website to “recognize” you as a unique individual. A cookie can’t read data off your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to recognize you when you return to our sites, or to identify which areas of our network of websites you have visited (i.e., Pastor Ray’s blog, sermons, etc.). We may use this information to better personalize the content you see on our sites.

Many websites place cookies on your hard drive. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Your browser can refuse all cookies, or show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

**Removing Your Name from our Mailing List.** Our website gives you the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list so that you do not receive any future communications from our ministry. If you desire to remove your name, you can send us an email at [info@KeepBelieving.com](mailto:info@KeepBelieving.com).

**Contacting Us.** If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send us an email at [info@KeepBelieving.com](mailto:info@KeepBelieving.com), or you can write to us at Keep Believing Ministries, Box 257, Elmhurst, IL  60126.

Ver. 02/07
